ora.tv 2018-11-09

# Ora.tv: Privacy Policy

Last Updated: May 3, 2016

This privacy policy (“Policy”) describes how ORA Media, LLC and its related companies (“Company”, “we” or “us”) collect, use and share personal information of consumer users of this website, www.ora.tv (the “Site”). This Policy also applies to any of our other websites that post this Policy. This Policy does not apply to websites that post different statements.

 **SITE NOT DIRECTED TO CHILDREN**  
We are concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet, and understand that children may not fully comprehend all of the provisions of our Privacy Policy or make informed decisions about the choices that are made available to adult users of the Site. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be familiar with the sites their children visit. Our Site is not directed to children under the age of 13, and we will never request information from anyone whom we know to be under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent. If we become aware that a user is under the age of 13 and has registered without prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her information from our files. 

**WHAT WE COLLECT**  
We get information about you in a range of ways. 

**Information You Give Us**.We collect your‎ name, email address as well as other information you directly give us on our Site.

 **Information Automatically Collected**. We automatically log information about you and your computer. For example, when visiting our Site, we log your computer operating system type, IP address, browser type, browser language, pages you viewed, how long you spent on a page, access times and information about your use of and actions on our Site. 

**Cookies**. We may log information using "cookies." Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Site.This type of information is collected to make the Site more useful to you and to tailor the experience with us to meet your special interests and needs. No personal information is gathered from these cookies. You can typically remove and reject cookies from our Site with your browser settings. Many browsers are set to accept cookies until you change your settings. If you remove or reject our cookies, it could affect how the Site works for you. In addition, third parties may place anonymous cookies on your browsers and may send their own cookies to the visitors' cookie file. These cookies may allow third parties and others to serve banners. Each banner may include a link that will include information for users on how to opt-out of being retargeted. 

**Advertisers**. We may allow third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our Site. Some of the advertising companies may directly or indirectly collect or use information about your visit to our Website to display advertisements more tailored to your interest. That information may include pages visited, content viewed, searches, clicks and purchases. If you want to know more about this practice, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) website at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) The NAI is a cooperative of online advertising companies who are committed to responsible practices and consumer protection. This site also uses PubMatic, Inc’s Sell Side Platform services. To read more about how PubMatic uses cookies or to opt out of PubMatic's cookie usage, please visit: <http://www.pubmatic.com/opt-out>.

USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use your personal information as follows:

  * We use your personal information to operate, maintain, and improve our sites, products, and services.
  * We use your personal information to process and deliver contest entries and rewards.
  * We use your personal information to respond to comments and questions and provide customer service.
  * We use your personal information to communicate about promotions, upcoming events, and other news about products and services offered by us and our selected partners.
  * We use your personal information to provide and deliver products and services customers request.

SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may share personal information as follows:

  * We may share personal information with your consent. For example, you may let us share personal information with others for their own marketing uses. Those uses will be subject to their privacy policies.
  * We may share personal information with our advertising partners in connection with contests and sweepstakes.
  * We may share personal information when we do a business deal, or negotiate a business deal, involving the sale or transfer of all or a part of our business or assets. These deals can include any merger, financing, acquisition, or bankruptcy transaction or proceeding.
  * We may share personal information for legal, protection, and safety purposes.
  * We may share information to comply with laws.
  * We may share information to respond to lawful requests and legal processes.
  * We may share information to protect the rights and property of Ora Media, LLC, our agents, customers, and others. This includes enforcing our agreements, policies, and terms of use.
  * We may share information in an emergency. This includes protecting the safety of our employees and agents, our customers, or any person.
  * We may share information with those who need it to do work for us.

We may also share aggregated and/or anonymized data with others for their own uses.

GENERAL WEBSITE TRAFFIC We keep track of total accesses to our site. All information gathered in this way is generic, and we do not track any individual users from this, but only calculate how many times the Site has been accessed. 

EMAIL IDENTIFICATION When a user sends a message to the Site, two pieces of information are automatically stamped on the message. These are, the time that the message was sent, and the Internet Provider (or IP) address it was sent from. This is done as a precaution against threatening emails we may receive that are directed towards Site staff, or anyone else. It is only ever used to find the source of a message in those extreme cases where we feel an individual’s safety may be at risk.

SOCIAL MEDIA SERVICES

Users may be able to access the Site through third-party social media platforms (such as Facebook) (each, a “Social Media Service”). If you log on to the Site through a Social Media Service, you give us permission to access, store and use any information that you permit the applicable Social Media Service to share with us in accordance with your privacy settings with the applicable Social Media Service. If you choose to log on to the Site through a Social Media Service, we are not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content of the applicable Social Media Service. We encourage you to review, and if necessary, adjust, your privacy settings with the applicable Social Media Service before logging in to the Site using the applicable Social Media Service. Information that we receive from Social Media Services is stored and use by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

SECURITY

The security of your personal information is important to us and we are committed to handling your information carefully. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard your personal information. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Although we use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

OTHER SITES

This Privacy Policy only applies to the Site. The Site may link from several points to third party websites. We have no control over third party privacy policies, which may differ from this Privacy Policy. Please examine the privacy policies of such third parties prior to submitting any personal information. Ora Media, LLC and its parent, affiliates, or service providers do not control the content that appears on any third party sites and do not endorse any of their products or services. Links to third party sites are provided solely for your convenience and any submission of data to such sites should be performed at your sole risk.

INFORMATION CHOICES AND CHANGES

Our marketing emails tell you how to “opt-out.” If you opt out, we may still send you non-marketing emails. Non-marketing emails include emails about our business dealings with you. You may send requests about personal information to our Contact Information below. You can request to change contact choices, opt-out of our sharing with others, and update your personal information. Following receipt of a request from you, we will take reasonable steps to delete your information. If your name, e-mail or other contact information changes you can make changes to your user information by emailing us at the Contact Information below. If you have a request or question relating to such information, including use by our affiliates for direct marketing purposes, you can email us by clicking the email address found in the Contact Information section below. Following receipt of a request from you, we will take reasonable steps to update or correct your information. We reserve the right to retain any information reasonably necessary to appropriately document our business activities and for archival and record retention purposes. We will store information about you for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code permits California residents to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information about the types of personal information the business has shared with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident, you may make one request each year by contacting us at the email address below. Under California Civil Code Section 1789.3, California Site users are entitled to the following specific consumer rights notice: The Complaint Assistance Unit of the Division of Consumer Services of the California Department of Consumer Affairs may be contacted in writing at 1625 North Market Blvd., Suite N 112, Sacramento, CA 95834 or by telephone at (800)-952-5210 or (916)-574-7950.

CONTACT INFORMATION

We welcome your comments or questions about this privacy policy. You may also contact us at our address:

Ora Media, LLC

40 FULTON ST., 11th FLOOR

New York, NY 10038

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. 

We may change this privacy policy. If we make any changes, we will change the Last Updated date above.
